

# FABIAN MASSOTTO

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

#### **PROFILE**

I am naturally curious and passionate about technology and innovation, devoted to keep learning every day. I love working in fast-paced and dynamic environments, with different cultures and backgrounds, where collaboration is key to success. A problem solver at heart, I approach challenging scenarios with a creative mindset and enjoy finding solutions.

### SKILLS

 Web Development Python DevOps o Django Cloud Azure Artificial Intelligence Terraform Automation GitHub JavaScript Docker TypeScript Backstage Storybook React.js

#### **EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS**

## **University of Buenos Aires**

Master's degree, Artificial Intelligence Mar 2024 - Present

## **Universidad Tecnológica Nacional**

Engineer's degree, Electronics Mar 2014 - Dec 2019

### **Harvard University**

CS50's: Artificial Intelligence
 CS50's: Web Development
 Jul - Nov 2023
 Jan - Apr 2023

#### Software certifications

•	Azure AI Engineer Associate	May 2024
•	GitHub foundations	Feb 2024
•	Azure AI fundamentals	Aug 2023
•	Azure Developer Associate	Jun 2023







## CAREER SUMMARY

#### **ExxonMobil**

Software Engineer

Jul 2020 - Present

Specialized in design and development of cloud-based web applications, my daily responsibilities involve every aspect of the web development lifecycle, including frontend and backend coding, CI/CD pipelines, infrastructure as code, and testing.

Over the past years, I have worked with various crossfunctional teams, providing guidance on web development best practices, diagnosing application performance issues, and identifying opportunities to enhance the developer experience across the organization.

Key experiences include:

- Development and support of the ExxonMobil's Design System using Storybook, ensuring a consistent and efficient UI/UX across all applications.
- Currently leading the development of an Internal Developer Portal, leveraging open-source Backstage framework, to streamline development processes and boost productivity for engineering teams.

## **Ernst & Young**

Software Engineer

Jun 2019 - Jul 2020

As a member of the Computer Forensics team, my main responsibilities involved engineering ETL pipelines to transform digital evidence into structured formats, making data accessible and actionable for auditors and fraud investigators.

#### CONTACT INFO

Country of origin: Argentina Email: massotto.fabian@gmail.com Phone: +54 9 11 3146 2971

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/massottofabian

GitHub: github.com/fabimass
Portfolio: fabianmassotto.vercel.app